So far in this email class we've looked at some tips that we need to keep in mind when we're writing
到目前为止，在这个电子邮件课程中，我们已经了解了一些在写作时需要牢记的技巧
emails.
电子邮件。
We've also looked at a personal email from Sarah to Kate.
我们还查看了莎拉发给凯特的个人电子邮件。
And now we're going to look at a professional email and how we can do one of these well some of the
现在我们要看看一封专业的电子邮件，以及我们如何才能做好其中的一些
basics.
基本。
The first thing you might notice here is that there is very little extra unnecessary stuff here.
您可能会在这里注意到的第一件事是，这里几乎没有多余的不必要的东西。
There is no FLUFF FLUFF as sort of stuff that's there but doesn't have much content.
没有 FLUFF FLUFF 之类的东西，但内容不多。
It's called fluff.
叫做绒毛。
It can be used in lots of different lots of different situations.
它可以用于许多不同的情况。
We also said flowery language no flowery language here at all.
我们也说华丽的语言，这里根本没有华丽的语言。
It's very concise very concise.
非常简洁非常简洁。
That means there's no fat no fluff.
这意味着没有脂肪没有绒毛。
No more is said than needs to be said.
无需多说，无需多说。
OK so let's read through the e-mail then we'll talk about it a bit.
好的，让我们通读电子邮件，然后我们将讨论一下。
Steve we got an order this week from a client in Canada.
史蒂夫，我们这周收到了来自加拿大客户的订单。
I need price estimates on materials for the following quantities.
我需要以下数量的材料价格估算。
Ten thousand medium sized balloons 300 hand pumps.
一万个中型气球300个手泵。
Get back to me A.S.A.P. with these estimates.
尽快回复我。有了这些估计。
Thanks Alan.
谢谢艾伦。
Very very succinct very very clear.
非常非常简洁非常清楚。
There's no way to misunderstand this.
没有办法误解这一点。
There's no long introduction paragraph like Hey Steve how are you doing.
没有像嘿史蒂夫你好吗这样的长介绍段落。
Hope the kids are well it's not usually necessary when you have two people who work together or know
希望孩子们一切都好，当你有两个一起工作或认识的人时，通常不需要
each other professionally it's not necessary get down to business get down to business don't waste time
彼此专业 没必要正事 正事 不要浪费时间
OK.
好的。
Now what is the relationship between Steve and Alan.
现在史蒂夫和艾伦之间的关系是什么。
Well they know each other very well.
好吧，他们彼此非常了解。
How do we know that.
我们怎么知道。
Well he just says his name.
好吧，他只是说出了他的名字。
He doesn't say Dear Steve doesn't use mister.
他没有说亲爱的史蒂夫不使用先生。
He doesn't say Hello there Steve.
他没有说你好，史蒂夫。
That would be OK but just saying Steve gives it a feeling of what these two probably communicate every
没关系，但只要说史蒂夫就给人一种这两个人可能每次交流的感觉
day or at least very very often.
一天，或者至少非常非常频繁。
Maybe a couple of times per week.
也许每周几次。
We got an order this week from a client in Canada so that means that Steve knows everything about what
本周我们从加拿大的一位客户那里得到了订单，这意味着史蒂夫对什么一无所知
an order means.
一个命令的意思。
So they have a previous history of working together and I need estimates on materials.
所以他们以前有过合作的历史，我需要对材料进行估算。
So they obviously they obviously have some previous history probably a lot and a pretty close working
所以他们显然有一些以前的历史可能很多而且工作非常密切
relationship.
关系。
Client is someone who maybe you're doing business with.
客户是可能与您有业务往来的人。
It's similar to a customer estimates.
这类似于客户的估计。
This is a close guess.
这是一个很接近的猜测。
Basically if someone says Can you give me an estimate on how much it would cost to fix my car that means
基本上，如果有人说你能给我估计修理我的车需要多少钱吗？
you're not telling me exactly how much it would cost to fix my car but you're trying to give me a close
你没有告诉我修理我的车要花多少钱，但你试图让我结束
number about nine hundred dollars.
数字约九百美元。
Well it might be more than 900.
那么它可能超过900。
It might be less than 900 but you're giving me an estimate.
它可能少于 900，但你给我一个估计。
That's a noun.
那是一个名词。
But estimate can be a verb is a verb.
但是估计可以是动词就是动词。
Estimate estimate different pronunciation.
估计估计不同的发音。
Same spelling on materials for the following quantities.
以下数量的材料拼写相同。
So we can often use this structure the following something I need the following.
所以我们可以经常使用这个结构下面的东西我需要的东西下面。
Please give me details on the following.
请给我以下的详细信息。
Then you use this to dots on top of each other.
然后你用这个点在彼此之上。
This is called a colon a colon and a colon is used when we're going to usually say some information
这称为冒号冒号，当我们通常要说一些信息时使用冒号
in order here.
在这里按顺序。
We've made a list of two things.
我们列出了两件事。59
This is a very good way of asking for something because it's not mixed in with the rest of the email
这是一种很好的询问方式，因为它不会与电子邮件的其余部分混在一起
with the body of the email.
与电子邮件的正文。
The first paragraph here it's separated.
这里的第一段是分开的。
That's very important because it can no longer be missed.
这非常重要，因为它不能再被错过。
He can not misunderstand.
他不能误会。
He needs these two things this and this and they're not even sentences.
他需要这两个东西这个和这个，它们甚至不是句子。
Please give me ten thousand medium sized balloons.
请给我一万个中型气球。
It's not even a sentence just says ten thousand medium sized balloons 300 hand pumps.
一句话都不说，一万个中型气球300个手泵。
If you make sentences it's more possible for there to be confusion.
如果您造句，则更有可能造成混淆。
So by keeping it very concise making lists for what we want.
因此，通过保持非常简洁，列出我们想要的内容。
Using the following and then a colon we're able to reduce the possibility of misunderstandings which
使用以下内容，然后使用冒号，我们能够减少误解的可能性
often happens.
经常发生。
And so the better our emails are the more clear they are the more likely we are to be efficient and
所以我们的电子邮件越好，越清晰，我们就越有可能变得高效和
communicate well with our our colleagues.
与我们的同事进行良好的沟通。
OK.
好的。
If you don't know what these things are it's not that important.
如果你不知道这些东西是什么，那并不重要。
These are just basically things that he needs.
这些基本上都是他需要的东西。
We're not going to worry too much about that then is giving him a little push.
我们不会太担心，然后给他一点推动力。
OK.
好的。
He could just stop there and say thanks Alan but he's giving him a bit of push and he's trying to give
他可以停下来对艾伦说声谢谢，但他给了他一点推动力，他试图给予
him a feeling of urgency.
他有一种紧迫感。
Hurry up a little bit OK.
快一点就好了。
Don't go slowly on this.
不要慢慢来。
Get back to me A.S.A.P. as soon as possible with these estimates as soon as possible this is very common
尽快回复我。尽快用这些估计 尽快 这很常见
as well.
也是。
And often at the end of an email like this you'll have one sentence that is just pushing a little bit.
通常在这样一封电子邮件的结尾，你会有一个句子，只是有点推动。
Please let me know as soon as you can or I'm really looking forward to hearing from you.
请尽快让我知道，否则我真的很期待收到您的来信。
There are a lot of sentences you can use like that.
你可以像这样使用很多句子。
We're going to go through a couple in just a minute.
我们将在一分钟内完成一对夫妇。
OK.
好的。
So you can use this structure basically this format when you're writing e-mails to your colleagues your
所以当你给你的同事写电子邮件时，你可以使用这种结构，基本上就是这种格式。
co-workers and they will probably appreciate you for being so clear the structure is introduction to
同事们，他们可能会感谢你如此清晰地介绍了结构
what I need or the situation specifically the things I need in a list set off by colon.
我需要什么或情况特别是我需要的东西在一个用冒号隔开的列表中。
Then a little push one sentence and then the name.
然后一点点推一个句子，然后是名字。
OK thanks is enough.
好的，谢谢就够了。
Thanks is enough.
谢谢就够了。
Could have said regards I guess thanks is probably better in this situation.
可以说问候我想在这种情况下感谢可能更好。